A Guide to the Charles F. Gillette, Papers, ca. 1880-1985 (bulk 1918-1969)
Library of Virginia
- Client Correspondence and Card File, 1921-1968.
  - Lambdin, Dr. J. W.- CCN 430 1961-1963 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2327
  - Lamm, W. T., Jr.- CCN 431 1951-1960 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 1053
  - Lane, Mrs.Bernard B.- CCN 432 1962-1964 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2349
  - Lane, E. H., Jr.- CCN 433 1939-1965 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2450
  - Lane, E. H., Sr.- CCN 434 1966 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 587
  - Langhorne, Miss Mae- CCN 435 1953-1957 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Larus, Mrs. Lewis- CCN 436 1942-1950 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 278
  - Latham, Arthur- CCN 959 1954 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2061
  - Lavenstein, Gerald- CCN 437 1959-1960 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2295
  - Laverge, Jan- CCN 438 1952 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 1078
  - Lawrenceville Cemetery, - CCN 439 1953-1960 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 2137
  - Lawyers Title Insurance Co., - CCN 440 1957-1959 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 2149
  - Layfield, Gaylon- CCN 441 1955-1964 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2055
  - Lee, Raymond H.- CCN 442 1957-1959 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2150
  - Lee, Robert E., Jr.- CCN 443 1954-1955 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 2033
  - Lees, James and Sons, Co., - CCN 444 1957 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Leggett, R. A.- CCN 445 1942-1943 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 734
  - Leggett, T. C.- CCN 446 1964 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2422
  - Lester, Victor C.- CCN 448 1958-1961 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2210
  - Lewis, Daniel C.- CCN 447 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2472
  - Lewis, James F., Jr.- CCN 449 1952-1957 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2233
  - Lewis, James F., Jr.- CCN 449 1959 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, James F., Jr.- CCN 449 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Lewis, James F., Jr.- CCN 449 1962-1968 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Liles, Dr. L. Carl- CCN 450 1946 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Lipsitz, Dave- CCN 451 1944-1963 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Livy, E. Bruce- CCN 452 1942-1947 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 763
  - Locher, Baldwin G.- CCN 453 1957-1959 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Locher & Co., - CCN 454 1942 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Lock Lane Apartments, - CCN 951 1944-1946 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 771
  - Longan, Dr.Robert C., Jr.- CCN 455 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2482
  - Longwood College, - CCN 459 1960-1962 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2290
  - Longwood College, - CCN 459 1963-1964 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Longwood College, - CCN 459 1965-1967 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Lorio Iron Works, - CCN 456 1946-1951 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Louthan, Frank, Jr.- CCN 460 1960 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2257
  - Love, Virginia- CCN 461 1965 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2444
  - Lowry, J. M.- CCN 462 1964-1966 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2403
  - Luck, Charles S., Jr.- CCN 1143, 1144 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    Gillette account numbers: 625, 671
  - Lund, Mrs.Joel Y.- CCN 457 1945-1946 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Lynch, Kenneth- CCN 458 1939-1966 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 633
  - Lynchburg City Beautification, - CCN 464 1949 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Lynchburg College, - CCN 463 1955 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - M General, 1942-1967 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - MacKintosh, Alexander- CCN 465 n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - MacKenzie, James C.- CCN 466 1944-1951 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Maclin, John H.- CCN 467 1945-1947 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 796
  - MacRae, Hugh, II- CCN 468 1952-1953 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Maddry, Charles E.- CCN 469 1944 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 759
  - Maderia School, - CCN 470 1944 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 355
  - Madison College, - CCN 471 1958 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2231
  - Mallory, Mrs.B. A.- CCN 472 1951-1954 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 1086
  - Manse, The (Woodrow Wilson Birthplace), - CCN 473 1941-1963 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 445
  - Maris, A. S.- CCN 481 1948-1949 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 904
  - Markel, Milton- CCN 474 1952 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 1068
  - Markel Service, Inc., - CCN 475 1953-1957 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 2020
  - Markel, Stanley- CCN 476 1951-1958 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 1036
  - Marks, Wirt P. Jr.- CCN 477 1949-1950 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Marks, Wirt P., Jr.- CCN 478 1951-1965 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2400
  - Marshall, Edwin J.- CCN 482 1942 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Marshall, Mrs.Gordon- CCN 483 1955-1956 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Marshall, Mrs.John- CCN 484 1954 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Marshburn, Col. Owen- CCN 485 1947-1949 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 902
  - Marston, Mrs. Oliver- CCN 486 1949-1954 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    Gillette account number: 1019
  - Martin, Dr.Berkeley H.- CCN 479 1958 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Martin, Fernando C.- CCN 487 1953-1955 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    Gillette account number: 1177
  - Martinsville General Hospital, - CCN 480 1946 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Marvin, Lucille M.- CCN 488 1950-1962 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 998
  - Mary Baldwin College, - CCN 489 1941-1960 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 502
  - Mary Baldwin College, - CCN 489 1961 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Mary Baldwin College, - CCN 489 1962-1965 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Mary Washington College, - CCN 490 1946-1966 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 841
  - Mason, Mrs.Charles E.- CCN 491 1942 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Massanetta Springs, - CCN 492 1961-1962 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2337
  - Massey, Ivor- CCN 493 1958-1966 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Massey, Mrs.William E.- CCN 494 1952 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Matthiessen, Ralph H.- CCN 495 1944-1951 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 782
  - Matthiessen, Ralph H.- CCN 495 1955-1964 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Mauck, Dr. H. Page- CCN 496 1950 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 561
  - Maury, Richmond- CCN 497 1966 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2240
  - May, Ralph- CCN 498 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2486
  - Mayo Episcopal Church House, - CCN 499 1965 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2438
  - McClellan, Mrs.John P.- CCN 500 1958 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2209
  - McConnell, Mrs.Samuel Parker- CCN 501 1955-1956 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2098
  - McCullough, Allen- CCN 502 1963 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - McElroy, Mrs.John Lee- CCN 503 1951-1965 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2329
  - McGowan, James P.- CCN 504 1957 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2181
  - McGuire Park, - CCN 505 1944 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 761
  - McIntosh, Courtney- CCN 506 1963 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - McIver, E. G.- CCN 507 1953 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 1126
  - McLaughlin, Mrs.Lee- CCN 508 1961-1962 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - McLelland, Dr. Robert- CCN 509 1958-1963 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 2218
  - McLeod, John E.- CCN 510 1955 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 1192
  - Meadowbrook Subdivision, - CCN 1228 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Mecklenburg Planning Commission, - CCN 511 1950-1951 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 1022
  - Meredith College, - CCN 513 1949-1963 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 1106
  - Metcalf, Houghton P.- CCN 512 1945-1948 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 801
  - Meyer, Vincent- CCN 514 1953 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 1042
  - Michigan State College, - CCN 515 1954 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Miller, Craig- CCN 516 1963 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Miller, J. Clifford, Jr.- CCN 517 1956-1968 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    Gillette account number: 662
  - Miller, Mrs.L. Gordon, Jr.- CCN 518 1960 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    Gillette account number: 2281
  - Millhiser, E. Ross- CCN 519 1943-1958 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2121
  - Millhiser, E. Ross- CCN 519 1959-1967 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Mills, Ellis H.- CCN 520 1943-1944 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 752
  - Minges, M. O.- CCN 521 1953 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 1159
  - Minor, Mrs. Philip M.- CCN 1250 ca. 1956-1966 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Mitchell, Dr.Howard L.- CCN 522 1957-1962 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2202
  - Molette, W. P.- CCN 523 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2246
  - Monk, R. T.- CCN 524 1953-1954 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Montreat Mountain Retreat Association, - CCN 1089 1950-1959 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 1102
  - Moore, Mrs. Charles Beatty- CCN 525 1960-1961 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2306
  - Moore, Mrs.J. Augustus- CCN 526 1952 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Moore, Mrs.John C.- CCN 1006 n.d. (Box 47, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2370
  - Moore, Richmond, Jr.- CCN 527 1964-1967 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 2395
  - Moore, T. Justin- CCN 528 1958-1965 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 2212
  - Moore, Dr.William- CCN 529 1952-1955 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 1101
  - Morgan, Edwin- CCN 530 1948-1951 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 897
  - Morgan, Irvin, Jr.- CCN 531 1952-1954 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 1137
  - Morgan, Samuel Tate, Jr.- CCN 532 1942-1967 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 49
  - Morrill, Stanwood- CCN 533 1946-1947 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 839
  - Morton, William- CCN 602 1957-1968 (Box 48)
    Gillette account number: 1148
  - Morris, A. M.- CCN 535 1946-1947 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 847
  - Morris, Mrs.Charles L.- CCN 534 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2262
  - Morten, Spencer- CCN 536 1957-1962 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2163
  - Morton, Carrie V.- CCN 537 1953-1954 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Morton, Dr.David C.- CCN 957 n.d. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 411
  - Motley, Frank R.- CCN 538 1959-1965 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2275
  - Mount Vernon Methodist Church, - CCN 540 1955-1958 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2058
  - Mountain View Subdivision, - CCN 539 1954-1958 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2018
  - Moyer, Richard- CCN 1046 1967 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2179
  - Mullinax, Perry F.- CCN 542 1947 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 862
  - Mumma, Robert A.- CCN 543 1948-1950 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 921
  - Munford, William Tayloe- CCN 544 1948-1950 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Murrell, Dr. Thomas W., Jr.- CCN 545 1951-1966 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 1051
  - Myers, Robert H.- CCN 547 1950 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Myers Park Baptist Church, - CCN 546 1950-1952 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 1028
  - Myrick, Lt. Richard B.- CCN 548 1945-1946 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Myrin, Lars B.- CCN 549 1946 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 809
  - N General, 1945-1965 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Nagel, Charles, Jr.- CCN 550 1942-1945 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Neal, Charles D., Jr.- CCN 551 1955-1957 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Neale, Mrs. Charles T.- CCN 552 1945-1947 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Nelson, Beverly T.- CCN 553 1942-1943 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    Gillette account number: 632
  - Newport News - Anderson Park, - CCN 554 1944-1945 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Newport News Water Works - Lee Hall, - CCN 555 1944-1946 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    Gillette account number: 789
  - Newton, Mrs.R. B.- CCN 556 1945-1948 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Nicholson, Henry- CCN 1086 1957 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Nimocks, Mrs. Q. K., III- CCN 558 1949-1950 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Nock, Mrs.Floyd, Jr.- CCN 559 1944 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Noell, C. E., Jr.- CCN 1047 n.d. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2068
  - Noland, Lloyd U., Jr.- CCN 560 1952-1958 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 1107
  - Nolde, Mrs. H. William- CCN 561 1942-1960 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 505
  - Nolte, Mrs. Frank- CCN 1229 1949-1959 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Norcum High School, - CCN 562 1952-1954 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 970
  - Norfolk Redevelopment and Housing Authority, - CCN 564 1950 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Norfolk, City of, - CCN 563 1943-1950 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 495
  - North Carolina State Fair, - CCN 565 1949 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - North Riverside Baptist Church, - CCN 1051 1961 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2326
  - Northrop, Mrs.William- CCN 567 1950-1965 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 1
  - Norton, E. Hope- CCN 568 1948-1952 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 889
  - Norton, E. Hope- CCN 568 1953-1955 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Norton, E. Hope- CCN 568 1956-1960 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Norwood Park Subdivision, - CCN 569 1947 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 855
  - Novak, Dr.John G.- CCN 570 1961-1965 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2325
  - November, Israel- CCN 571 1944-1965 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2321
  - Ober, Woodbury S.- CCN 572 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 802
  - Ober, Woodbury S.- CCN 572 1947-1948 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Ober, Woodbury S.- CCN 572 1949-1951 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Ober, Woodbury S. (Spicer Mill Farm Subdivision)- CCN 573 1952-1955 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2034
  - Ober, Woodbury S. (Spicer Mill Farm Subdivision)- CCN 573 1956-1968 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Obici Memorial Hospital Grounds, - CCN 574 1950-1963 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 1034
  - O'Ferrall, Mrs. T. McLain- CCN 575 1944 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 768
  - Officer's Club, - CCN 576 1959 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - O'Hara, L. R.- CCN 577 n.d. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Ohio State University, - CCN 578 1946 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Old Dominion College, - CCN 579 1964-1965 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Old Swedes Church, - CCN 580 1945-1948 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 806
  - Oleander Corporation, - CCN 581 1955 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2067
  - Orange Episcopal Church, - CCN 582 1960 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Ormond, H. L.- CCN 583 1952 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Orton Plantation, - CCN 584 n.d. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2065
  - Our Lady of Grace Church, - CCN 585 1952-1953 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 1084
  - Our Lady of Perpetual Help Church, - CCN 586 1952 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Overby, Mrs. Dudley- CCN 587 1951 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Overman, Mrs.Cyrus- CCN 588 1958 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 2214
  - Owens and Minor- CCN 1249 n.d. (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Owens, L. B.- CCN 589 1956 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Owsley, Mrs. Frederick- CCN 590 1945-1947 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 503
  - P General, 1944-1965 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Page, R. B.- CCN 592 1950 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 906
  - Page House, - CCN 591 1965 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Palmer, Meade- CCN 594 1942-1962 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Palmer, Mrs. Malvern H.- CCN 593 1948-1950 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    Gillette account number: 967
  - Pangman, John- CCN 595 1954-1957 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 1195
  - Paris, Leonard A.- CCN 596 1964-1965 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2424
  - Park, G. S.- CCN 597 1953-1956 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 1168
  - Parker, Mrs. Elwood- CCN 598 1954 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2014
  - Parker, Mrs.George H.- CCN 599 1947-1948 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Parrish, J. Scott- CCN 600 1941-1945 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 104
  - Parrott, J. Frank- CCN 601 1950-1951 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Parsons, James Henry- CCN 1230 1957-1968 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Parsons, Mrs.Jessie H.- CCN 614 1964-1965 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Parsons, Mrs.Mary (Dover Rd.)- CCN 603 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2177
  - Parsons, Mrs. Mary (Sulgrave Rd.)- CCN 604 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2270
  - Parsons, Mrs.Mary (Sulgrave Rd.)- CCN 604 1961 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Parsons, Mrs.Mary (Sulgrave Rd.)- CCN 604 1962-1963 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Pasco, E. R.- CCN 618 1963 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 1103
  - Pate, Edwin- CCN 615 1948-1949 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Patrick Henry Airport, - CCN 616 1965-1966 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2454
  - Patterson, E. R.- CCN 617 1945-1965 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 794
  - Patterson, Frank E.- CCN 605 1946 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Paxton, M. W., Jr.- CCN 619 1957-1959 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Pearce, E. L.- CCN 620 1949-1950 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Pearsall, Mrs.John W.- CCN 622 1955 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 1043
  - Pearsall, Mrs.Leon M.- CCN 606 1945 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Pearsall, William- CCN 621 1953 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 1167
  - Peebles, C. W.- CCN 623 1956-1957 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2126
  - Pembleton, Dr. W. E.- CCN 624 1951 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 1049
  - Peple, Dr. W. L., Jr.- CCN 625 1962 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Perkins, Mrs.William R., Jr.- CCN 631 1953 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 1136
  - Perry, Mrs.W. D.- CCN 626 1940-1952 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 642
  - Pershing, John- CCN 627 1956-1964 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 2124
  - Peter, Mrs. G. Freeland- CCN 628 1943-1967 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Peter, W. F.- CCN 629 1952-1954 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Peters, A. Winnett- CCN 630 1957 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2164
  - Petersburg General Hospital, - CCN 632 1967 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2426
  - Petersburg Home for Ladies, - CCN 1182 1958-1966 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2230
  - Pettey, Herbert L.- CCN 634 1952-1956 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 1125
  - Pettus, Hunter R.- CCN 1072 n.d. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 913
  - Petty, William G.- CCN 635 1964-1966 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2419
  - Philip Morris- McComas Research Center, - CCN 636 1958-1963 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2215
  - Piccirilli, [unknown]- CCN 607 1963 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Pinner, Henry M.- CCN 637 1946-1947 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 540
  - Plonk, Dr.George W.- CCN 638 1954 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2023
  - Poe, Dr.Clarence- CCN 639 1942-1946 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 562
  - Poe, Dr.Clarence- CCN 639 1947-1962 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Poe, Harvey L.- CCN 641 1955-1956 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2085
  - Poe Foundation (Mrs. Corbin Old), - CCN 640 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 2416
  - Pollard, Mrs.Oliver A.- CCN 642 1957 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Porter, Knox D.- CCN 609 1949-1959 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Portsmouth Playground, - CCN 643 1950-1953 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Potter, Horatio- CCN 608 1945-1947 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Powell, Charles C.- CCN 644 1954 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Powers, W. Frank- CCN 645 1946-1948 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 887
  - Powers, W. Frank (Cemetery Plot and Memorial)- CCN 646 1949 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 937
  - Pratt, Dr.Frank- CCN 647 1954 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 1184
  - Pratt, John Lee- CCN 610 1943-1954 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 417
  - Presbyterian General Assembly's Training School for Lay Workers, - CCN 276 1958 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2236
  - Presbyterian Orphans' Home, Barium Springs, NC, - CCN 648 1945-1946 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Presbyterian Orphanage, Lynchburg, VA, - CCN 1001 n.d. (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 163
  - President Madison Inn, - CCN 649 1960 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Prillaman, Mrs. W. H.- CCN 650 1957-1958 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 2160
  - Proctor, W. H.- CCN 651 1949-1952 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 929
  - Protestant Episcopal Seminary, - CCN 652 1955-1960 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 2060
  - Pusey, Paul H.- CCN 653 1961-1962 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2320
  - Pusey, Mrs. W. W.- CCN 656 1959-1961 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2282
  - Putney, Walter- CCN 654 1953-1960 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 1140
  - Putzel, Henry V.- CCN 655 1942-1956 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 664
  - R General, 1944-1956 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Raab, Merril E.- CCN 657 1942-1951 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    Gillette account number: 224
  - Rabil, Albert- CCN 658 1950-1952 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    Gillette account number: 1015
  - Ragsdale, Mrs. Hugh- CCN 659 1951-1955 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    Gillette account number: 1057
  - Ragsdale, Mrs. W. G., Jr.- CCN 660 1944 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Raleigh, NC, Garden Club, - CCN 661 1948 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Randolph, E. Fairfax- CCN 662 1942-1964 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    Gillette account number: 709
  - Randolph, J. H., Jr.- CCN 663 1954 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    Gillette account number: 1191
  - Randolph, O. Robbins- CCN 668 1955-1959 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Randolph-Macon College, - CCN 664 1944-1945 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    Gillette account number: 770
  - Randolph-Macon College, - CCN 665 1962 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    Gillette account number: 2339
  - Randolph-Macon College, - CCN 666 1962 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    Gillette account number: 2347
  - Randolph-Macon Woman's College, - CCN 667 1947-1964 (Box 55, Folder 32)
    Gillette account number: 2409
  - Raney, Dr. R. B.- CCN 669 1952-1953 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Rawles, Benjamin W., Jr.- CCN 670 1944-1965 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Rawles, James W.- CCN 671 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2375
  - Rawles, Rena (Subdivision)- CCN 672 1961-1964 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2356
  - Rawles, Sol W., Jr.- CCN 673 1946-1965 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 819
  - Rawles, Sol W., Sr.- CCN 674 1952-1968 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 823
  - Rawles, Walter Cecil Library, - CCN 675 1957 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2170
  - Ray, Dr.Burton J.- CCN 676 1947 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 861
  - Ray, Mrs.John E., III- CCN 677 1953-1958 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 811
  - Read, Mrs.Charles Lathrop- CCN 679 1958 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 1112
  - Read, Mrs.William Alexander- CCN 678 1952-1955 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 1123
  - Reed, Leslie H.- CCN 680 1941-1943 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 74
  - Rehder, Henry- CCN 681 1954-1958 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Reil, John T.- CCN 702 1964 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 2412
  - Renard, Mrs. Wallace- CCN 682 1942 (Box 56, Folder 15)